treepodia.com 2017-01-16

# 

             Treepodia Website and Ecommerce Video Platform - Privacy Policy
                                  Updated: December 10, 2015
Treepodia's Ecommerce Video Platform (the "Platform"), provided by Treepodia Ltd.
("Treepodia", "we" or "us") through Treepodia's website (www.treepodia.com, the "Website")
as well as through Treepodia's clients' websites ("Third Party Websites", and together with the
Website, the "Websites"), is a powerful ecommerce video platform for online retailers enabling
them to cover their entire product catalog with dynamic and up-to-date product videos
instantaneously, and embed these videos in their websites using a customized video player,
through which certain user and viewer (you, the "user") information (including personal
information) is collected and analyzed by us.
We take the protection of the Websites' and Platform's users personal information very
seriously. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") explains how we collect such personal information,
how we use it and governs your use of the Website and the Platform.
By using any of the Websites, the Platform and/or providing us with any personal information
(or access to such information), you consent to the terms of this Policy and to the practices
described herein, and acknowledge that you are not required by law to provide such personal
information to us, and do so willingly and in agreement with this Policy.
Please note that your personal information may be processed in countries where laws regarding
processing of personal information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.
Information We Collect
We collect information about you from various sources, including the following:
   Contacts
    We collect any information contained in e-mails or other messages that you send us,
    including through our contact forms on our Website.
   Technical Information
    We receive data from the computer, mobile phone or other device you use to access and use
    any of the Websites and/or Platform. This may include your IP address, the type of your
    browser, system, device and language, date and time of visits, the type of your internet

    service, location, the pages you visit, and the way that you interact with any of the Websites
    and/or Platform, videos, ads and other types of content therein.
   Information from Third Parties
    We may regularly receive information from our business partners, advertising agencies,
    customers and other third parties. Such information helps us and them understand videos and
    ads delivery and online activity, and generally better the Websites, the Platform and the
    videos provided therein.
How We Collect Information
Our primary source of information is the information provided to us by you. Other sources of
information include various third parties, as set forth above, and standard web technologies,
including the following:
   "Cookies" - data files, which often include a unique identifier, sent to your browser and
    placed on your computer or mobile device in order to enable you to more easily use the
    Websites and Platform and store certain information, and to enable us to provide you with
    more relevant content, ads and special offers. We may use both session cookies (which
    expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your device
    until you delete them). Usually you can set your web browser to refuse all cookies or to
    indicate when a cookie is being received. However, some features of the Websites and
    Platform may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. Please note
    that as you access the Platform from any third party website, then the content included
    therein, such as ads, may be provided by third parties, and may also contain and send
    cookies to your computer or mobile device.
   "Beacons" or "Pixels" - electronic files used to track your uses and navigation through the
    Website, Platform and Third Party Websites using the Platform, the completion of
    transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior.
   "Log Files" – when you use any of the Websites and/or Platform we may track and record
    actions occurring on the Websites and/or Platform and collect certain technical data
    including your IP address, device and browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit
    pages, system type, date/time stamp, click data, viewing behavior and types of
    advertisements viewed.

How We Generally Use the Information
We use the information we collect, first, to better provide you with the Websites, the Platform
and the videos therein. We put together all the information available to us to maximize the
relevance and quality of the Website and Platform's videos and content. For example, we use the
information that we collect in order to: (a) provide personalized advertising, content and
information to our users; (b) monitor and improve the effectiveness of the Websites and
Platform's videos and content and our clients' marketing; (c) monitor aggregate metrics and
statistical information regarding the Websites and Platform and their users; and (d) diagnose or
fix technology problems reported by our clients, users or engineers.
We also use the information we collect for purposes of administering and improving the
Websites and the Platform, monitoring users' activities and purchases during and/or subsequent
to their use of the Platform, making available more relevant videos and content to our users and
prospective users, and enabling Third Party Websites, clients and advertisers to deliver general
and targeted ad and video content to you.
Occasionally, we may also use your contact information (if provided by you through your
contacts with us) to contact you and notify you about new services and special opportunities we
think you will find valuable, on our behalf and on behalf of our partners. We may contact you
by phone, mail or email (if you have provided us with such information), as well as through the
Websites, the Platform, and other similar channels. By providing us with your contact
information you consent to our use of such contract information to send you such notices, and
any notices required by law. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish us to send you
promotional communications, by emailing us at unsubscribe@treepodia.com, or by clicking
"unsubscribe" in the message.
We may provide third parties with certain information about you without identifying you as an
individual. We do this for purposes such as (1) providing our clients, advertisers and advertising
agencies with information that allows them to present targeted personalized ads and promotions;
(2) providing our clients and advertisers with information required to diagnose and resole any
commercial and accounting issues with regards to the Platform and its users; (3) providing
statistical and aggregated data to researchers and other data consumers; (4) analyzing how the
Platform is used; (5) diagnosing and resolving technical problems; (6) maintaining security. We
reserve the right to use and disclose any anonymized information at our discretion.

Personally Identifying Information
The information you provide us will include Personally Identifying Information ("PII") which is
information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate or otherwise identify you.
We do not collect PII except when provided voluntarily by you directly. We do not rent, sell or
disseminate PII to third parties without your consent, other than:
   disclosure to our employees, consultants, contractors, business partners, clients, service
    providers and suppliers. Such disclosure is normally subject to the recipient's undertaking of
    confidentiality obligations and the prevention of any independent right to use this
    information by the recipients, except as required to help us provide the Website and the
    Platform.
   to comply with applicable laws and regulations or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant
    or other lawful request for information we receive, whether or not a response is required by
    applicable law;
   to enforce an agreement or to protect our rights;
   with any of our parent, or affiliated or successor entity;
   to consummate, and as part of, any asset sale, transfer, merger or liquidation;
We only provide data to our advertising partners after we have removed your name or any other
personally identifying information from it, or have combined it with other people's data in a way
that it is no longer associated with you. As stated above, we may allow third-party advertising
agencies and networks to serve advertisements, or may ourselves serve advertisements, through
the Websites and/or Platform. Such ads may be based on the information provided to us, other
than the PII. We do not provide any PII to such advertising agencies and networks. However,
please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain type of users or
audience, and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that
you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. You should consult the respective
privacy policies of advertising agencies and networks. This Policy does not apply to, and we
cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Any solicitation of personal information
through such advertisements is strictly between the advertiser and you.
You may choose voluntarily whether or not to provide us with your PII. Notices provided at the
Platform and the Websites where we collect PII should help you to make this choice. If you
choose to avoid provision of your PII as we request it, you may be unable to access and use
certain options, offers and services available through the Websites and/or Platform and/or that
involve our interaction with you. You may request access to all your voluntarily-provided PII

that we collected online and maintain in our database by sending a written request to
info@treepodia.com.
Deactivation and Deletion of Your Information
If you want to delete or remove your PII stored with us permanently, you may send an e-mail to
unsubscribe@treepodia.com. Please include "Delete my Information" in the subject line and
your full name and e-mail address in the body of the e-mail. We will respond to your request in
a timely manner, normally within thirty (30) days. Upon such request, we will make our best
efforts to remove all your PII from our database. However, please note that some information
may not be deleted from all databases and backup records. We may also retain certain PII for
client and user service, legal and similar purposes. We reserve the right to keep all non-PII and
continue to use such non-PII in accordance with this Policy after the deletion of all your PII.
Information Security
We use industry standard measures to ensure the security of all information, including the use of
passwords, firewalls, encryption and remote servers, and routinely evaluate our practices to
identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our Website and Platform.
However, no transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure.
Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may
compromise information security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when
using the Websites and Platform and/or when communicating with us.
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or
knowingly allow such persons to use the Websites and Platform. If you are under 13, please do
not use any of the Websites and Platform and do not send any information about yourself to us.
No one under the age of 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to us. In the event
that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without
verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you
believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us
promptly at info@treepodia.com.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
By using the Websites and/or Platform you consent to our collection and use of your personal

information as described in this Policy. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will
notify you by placing a post regarding those changes on any of the Websites, the Platform
and/or by other means, as per our sole discretion. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at
any time, so please review it frequently. Changes to this Policy are binding and effective when
they are posted on this page.
Opting Out
You may opt out of Treepodia's use of cookies by visiting the Treepodia advertising opt-out
page.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Policy, our information practices, or your dealings with us,
you can contact us at info@treepodia.com.
